Sentence #,Word,Tag
Sentence: 1,My,O
1,name,O
1,is,O
1,annijoice,B-per
1,from,O
1,London,B-geo
2,Here,O
2,Muruga,B-per
3,This,O
3,is,O
3,Thalapathy,B-per
3,from,O
3,puliampatty,B-geo
